

# Le Trung Dung

**1**9/12/2002

**(**+84)842824902

Phuc La, Ha Dong, Ha Noi

**♥** Male

▼ trungdungle1912@gmail.com

https://www.facebook.com/dungg.trung .5

Position: Java Intern

## **SUMMARY**

The third year student majoring in Software Engineering at FPT University has experience in Java/JSP/Servlet and basic in React web programming. I look forward to leveraging my skills and knowledge to contribute to the company as a ReactJS Intern.

### **EDUCATION**

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING (SPECIALIZED FIELD: NODEJS -REACTJS)

10/2020 - Present

#### **FPT UNIVERSITY - HA NOI**

GPA: 3.08/4

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **DEVELOPER**

04/2023 - Present

#### <QUIZ/ANSWER TEST BY REACTJS>

<CRUD EMPLOYEE REACTJS>

REACTJS platform to do this short project.

- A Project with 1 developer has been built by HTML, CSS, JS, and React to design front-end and call API with Postman, Docker, and DBeaver to save the table data of the project and test the API of the project.
- The project allows users to attend and answer all of the list questions, which are created by the admin, within the admin can do CRUD with question/answer or update the status, and information of the user with a paginated table of data. All of the features also do by calling API and saving in the database.

• The project allow enterprise can manage their employee with basic CRUD function

all of data save in Local Storage, The project is used HTML, CSS, JS, JSON on

• Github: https://github.com/TrungDung1912/ReactJSCRUD.git

· Github: https://github.com/TrungDung1912/QuizTest.git

#### **DEVELOPER**

03/2023 -

## <PLAYER MUSIC G2>

- The small project is done by HTML, CSS, and JS Core. The project allows people who are music nerds can have an individual music area, where all of the list captivating songs help them chill out or let their hair down after tiring days.
- Github: https://github.com/TrungDung1912/MusicPlayerG2.git

#### **DEVELOPER**

04/2023 -

#### LEADER, DEVELOPER, TESTER

01/2023 - 04/2023

#### FPT UNIVERSITY - HA NOI < ONLINE DEBIT BOOK>

- Act as the team leader (team of 5 members) throughout the project
  Successfully designed online debit software allow user can access and CRUD with the debt. The system use Java Servlet, SQL Server, HTML, CSS, JS.
- Manage project progress and divide work, make project reports for members
- · Analyze, test, program and write product reports
- Gitlab: https://gitlab.com/maitranhuy1709/SWP\_SE1640\_GR3.git

#### DEVELOPER, TESTER

09/2022 - 11/2022

#### FPT UNIVERSITY - HA NOI < ATTENDANCE SYSTEM>

- Successfully designed attendance software for lecturers and students allow lecture can check attend to the student. The system use Java Servlet, SQL Server, HTML, CSS
- Project progress management
- Analyze, test and program, write product reports
- Github: https://github.com/TrungDung1912/IOT1601\_PRJ301\_ASS.git

## ADVANCED SKILL

- Read, Listen, Write, Speak to English document  $\sim 6.5$  IELTS
- · Gitlab/ Github
- Apache Netbeans IDE 13 / Apache Tomcat 8.5
- · Microsoft SQL Server Management Studio 18

### **AWARDS**

Excellent student of the term: Fall2022

FPT University Scholarship: 70%

## **BASIC SKILL**

- Teamwork
- · Flexible / Adaptable
- · Diligent / Perfectionist / Careful
- Communication

## **CERTIFICATES**

CertNexus Certified Ethical Emerging Technologist

01/2023

Software Development Lifecycle from the University of Minnesota

09/2022

Web Design for Everybody: Basic of Web Development & Coding from University of Michigan

06/2022

Computer Communications from University of Colorado System

01/2022

Academic Skills for University Success from the University of Sydney

09/2021

## **ACTIVITY**

LOGISTICS BOARD	VNEXPRESS MARATHON HANOI
11/2020 - 11/2022	The volunteer of VnExpress Marathon Hanoi Midnight 2020 / 2022

LOGISTICS BOARD F-CAMP FPTU

10/2020 - Present The logistic board of Fcamp 2020 / 2021/ 2022/ 2023

CULTURE BOARD VI TÉT FPTU

02/2021 - 03/2021 The culture board of Vị tết 2021